

kulsha_85@mail.ru +375 29 5678601 site: <u>vitalikulsha.github.io</u>

Junior Java Developer

Belarus, Zhodino

Skype: vitali kulsha Linkedin: vitali-kulsha Github: vitalikulsha VK: vitali kulsha

I work as a leading process engineer. Extensive experience in design and 3D modeling (KOMPAS, SolidWorks, Inventor, ProEngineer). I am developing in JAVA development. I am taking the Java Basics Upskill online course at EPAM, as well as various webinars, marathons and free courses.

Hard skills

Maven Java Spring **HTML** Junit IntelliJ IDEA

Git

Foreign languages

English — Elementary (Beginer)

Education

BNTU | MEF

«Tool production technology» Higher education | 09.2005 - 06.2011

Courses

EPAM | Online | 11.2020 - 03.2021 Course "Java Basics"

EPAM | Online | 03.2021 - until now

Course "Java Basics Upskill Lab"

ITVDN | Online | 07.2021 - 09.2021

Course "Java Developer"

Certificate for Testprovider:

TP69745306 - Java Starter

TP35933273 - Java EE Basics

TP28332316 - JDBC & Hibernate

TP72998692 - Git basics

TP59390149 - Spring

TP11562388 - Building Applications with Spring Data

Java Guru | Online | 02.2021 - 03.2021

Course "RPA (telegram bot)"

ITEA | Online | 09.2021 - 09.2021 Course "HTML-marathon"

Java Rush | Online | 08.2020 - until now Course "Java Syntax & Core"

Soft skills

- Sociability
- A responsibility
- Quick learning
- Tenacity
- Organization
- Initiative

Work experience

Leading Process Engineer

CJSC Belgee | Borisov district

08.2020 - until now

Ensuring the technology and quality of production of bodies in the welding workshop

Workshop foreman

CJSC Belgee | Borisov district

07.2016 - 08.2020

Personnel management, support for the production of bodies in the welding workshop

Process Engineer

LLC Belavtozapchast | Zhodino

02.2015 - 07.2016

Hydraulic cylinder production technology

Design engineer

LLC Snackpro | Smolevichi district

05.2013 - 01.2015

Design of units and mechanisms for the food industry

Design engineer

LLC Belavtozapchast | Zhodino

10.2010 - 05.2012

Construction of special devices and hydraulic cylinders

Head Office

JSC HFP | Zhodino

02.2008 - 10.2010

Personnel management, development of control programs for **CNC** machines

Design engineer

JSC HFP | Zhodino

08.2005 - 02.2008

Development of software for CNC machines, design of special devices

Projects

Java Learning Projects

Learning Projects for courses at EPAM, Java GURU, Java Rush, ITEA, telegram bot projects https://github.com/vitalikulsha

Construction work projects

Selective construction and 3D-modeling work projects in KOMPAS, Inventor, ProEngineer

https://kulsha85.wixsite.com/engineer/